eglinfcu.org 2016-10-22

# Eglin Federal Credit Union | Auto Loans, Mortgage Services and MasterCards

  |  |  |   |    

* * *

| FACTS | **WHAT DOES EGLIN FEDERAL CREDIT UNION DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
---|---  
Why? | Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.  
What? |  The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include: 

  * Social Security number and payment history 
  * Account balances and transaction history 
  * Account information 

How? | All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’ personal information; the reasons Eglin Federal chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.  

Reasons we can share your personal information | Does Eglin Federal share? | Can you limit this sharing?  
---|---|---  
**For our everyday business purposes** -  
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus | **Yes** | **No**  
**For our marketing purposes** -  
to offer our products and services to you | **Yes** | **No**  
**For joint marketing with other financial companies** | **Yes** | **Yes** *  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes** -  
information about your transactions and experiences | **No** | **We do not share**  
**For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes** -  
information about your credit worthiness | **No** | **We do not share**  
**For nonaffiliates to market to you** | **No** | **We do not share**  
  
To limit our sharing  
for joint marketing  
or for any questions: | 
* Call 850-862-0111 ext. 1402 or  

* Toll Free 1-800-367-6159 ext. 1402

*If you have previously opted out with Eglin Federal, you do not need to do so again.   
  
---|---  

Who we are  
---  
**Who is providing this notice?** | Eglin Federal Credit Union  

What we do  
---  
**How does Eglin Federal protect my personal information?** |  To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. 

These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings. Eglin Federal regularly monitors and tests security systems, trains employees, and makes necessary enhancements that conform to leading industry practices.  
  
**How does Eglin Federal collect my information?** |  We collect your personal information, for example, when you: 

  * Open an account or apply for a loan 
  * Use your debit or credit card and other electronic services 
  * Authorize debits or credits to your account 

We also collect your personal information from others, such as consumer credit reporting agencies.   
**Why can’t I limit all my sharing?** |  Federal law gives you the right to limit only 

  * sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes - information about your credit worthiness  

  * affliliates from using your information to market to you  

  * sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you 

Definitions  
---  
**Affiliates** |  Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. 

  * Eglin Federal has no affiliates. 

**Nonaffiliates** |  Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. 

  * Eglin Federal does not share with nonaffiliates. 

**Joint marketing** |  A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you. 

  * Our joint marketing partners include investment, insurance, and debt and asset protection products. 

  |  |   |    
AUTO RATES

As low as 1.99% APR. Stop in at local preferred dealers in Okaloosa or Escambia County and process your EFCU loan at the dealership.

Apply online for a PAL (pre-approved loan) to take to any licensed dealership in the USA. 

Visit AutoSMARTTM to locate new or used vehicles available in your area.  
View Auto Rates

* * *

MASTERCARD

Compare, switch, and save with our low-cost credit cards: Platinum MasterCard® or ScoreCard® with Rewards. Both cards have no balance transfer fee, no annual fee, no cash advance fee and only 1.1% International Transaction Fee.  
View MasterCard

* * *

HOME LOANS

We finance new home purchases in 7 Florida counties. Compare our rates and low fees and enjoy the savings! Looking to refinance or make home improvements? We can help with that too!  
View Mortgage Rates
